What if I told you that this entire pint
of the Tonight protein Ice Cream has
just 334 calories and packs 33 g of
protein? Let me show you how to make it.
You're going to need one of your
favorite chocolate protein shakes. And
then you're going to add your dry
ingredients, which are sweetener, cocoa
powder, salt, and zantham gum. And then
blend that all together with a hand
mixer. Throw your cover on and put it in
the freezer for at least 16 hours. Once
it's nice and frozen, you can take it
out and run it under hot water for about
a minute. and then throw it in your
creamy on the light ice cream setting.
Mine came out a little bit powdery, but
that is so fine. Just use the respin
setting and it'll come out absolutely
perfect. Also, before you guys comment
about it, I know that the Tonight also
has caramel ice cream, but to combine
two flavors in the Ninja Creamy, you
have to make two different pints. And
it's a whole process that I know you
aren't going to do. So, I decided to
make it easier for you and make that
decision for you. In terms of toppings,
I used just some random cookie dough I
found in our freezer. Yeah, it's
probably going to give you salmonella,
but I don't really care. And then I
threw in two Oreo thins on top with the
cream removed cuz they're only like 20
calories each.